Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org
[suspenseful music playing]
Gentlemen, I'm gonna need you
to bring your A game
if we're gonna beat Aurelita
again in the final.
I mean, they're gonna be out for blood,
and we're gonna be on their turf.
So don't think
just 'cause we beat them once
this is going to be an easy ride.
I need every single one of you
to bring it.
So go home. Get some rest.
I'll see you tomorrow.
-[Dylan] Let's go, boys.
-[player] Thanks, Coach.
-[player 2] Thanks, Coach.
-[indistinct chatter]
[Dylan] All right.
What do you think of our chances?
I mean, if Dylan keeps his form up,
I think we got one. [chuckles]
You know, I don't know how his dad
persuaded Principal Whitmore
to let him back on the team,
but to be honest, I'm kinda glad he did.
Since we lost you,
he's pretty much all we got.
[pensive music playing]
I always help my dad
organize the food stall,
so I'll be there from around 2:00 p.m.
Right. Maybe I can help
show them where to set up.
That's okay. We got it.
Dad's pretty much
already arranged everything.
I'm just there for backup.
Okay. So, Grace, we'll go together.
Yeah. Well, actually,
I'm getting there early
to set up the church raffle.
I could do that. What time?
I mean, we've got plenty of volunteers.
I'll just see you when you get there?
You should probably take it easy for once.
Yeah. Just enjoy your day.
-Okay.
-What is it?
I guess I'm just looking for
a distraction.
I have my driver's test in the morning,
and I'm really nervous.
I have to pass this time.
You will. You'll do great.
Yeah, I hope so.
-I'm gonna head out.
-I'm coming.
-Okay. Perfect.
-You got this, Jackie.
-Bye.
-[Skylar] See you.
-[upbeat country music playing]
-[horse neighs]
[Alex] Come on! [hooting, grunting]
[horn blares]
[men shout indistinctly]
[Alex sighs]
Any notes?
[Blake] You know what, Walter?
You're looking like
a real rider out there.
I'm impressed. [chuckles]
You think I'm, uh, gonna be ready
for the tryouts tomorrow?
I really need that sponsorship.
Yeah. I wouldn't let you
go out there if I didn't.
It's my reputation on the line too.
[chuckles]
You've come a long way, Alex Walter.
Yeah, well, it's pretty much
all thanks to you, right?
Look, I'll take the credit,
but you've put the work in.
Long hours, early mornings.
I can coach you all day long.
But you're the only one
who can make yourself better.
And you've done that.
[tender music playing]
Why does that sound like a goodbye?
If my dad decides to sponsor you tomorrow,
then I won't be your trainer anymore.
[pensive music playing]
[Dylan] That was hilarious.
Yo, I'll catch up with you guys later.
Why are you still here?
I'm trying to finish these
to sell at the Sparkle.
Oh. Cute.
So, you're still not talking to me, huh?
[sighs] What do you want me to say, Dylan?
Did you think I'd be okay with you
trying to cheat on a drug test
and then getting your dad
to bribe the school?
He didn't bribe the school.
But he still made everything okay, right?
[Dylan sighs]
Look, I was desperate.
Okay, if I don't play, then I might not
get to go to the showcase.
If I don't get into the showcase,
then I don't play college football.
And if I don't do that, my dad
will not speak to me till I'm like… 40.
So?
Is that all that matters?
You being a good boy for your daddy?
Why don't you stand up to him?
Don't you want to be your own person?
I don't know if I can.
I have to finish these.
[Dylan sighs]
[sighs]
[vehicle approaching]
That was perfect.
-I think you got it.
-Really?
Absolutely.
You're gonna pass this time, 100%.
Positive vibes only.
Okay. [chuckles]
-Hey, bud.
-Hi.
[Jackie] Hi.
How's it going?
It's going.
Big game tomorrow, huh?
Yep.
Well, you'll do great.
Um, I haven't seen you much
since Halloween.
Yeah, I know.
You know, Tony's, coaching,
and studying. It's just kinda--
Have you gotten
your new SAT scores back yet?
No.
Oh.
I feel like they should've come through.
Maybe you should call.
Yeah, you're right. I will. Thanks.
Do you wanna work on
college applications together
like we talked about?
No. That's okay.
We're kind of running out of time.
-I mean, I could do a first pass for you--
-Jackie, just leave it.
I gotta get back to these plays.
Like you said, tomorrow's a big day.
So…
Okay. Good luck.
[Cole] Yeah.
You too.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[emotional music playing]
[sighs]
[door opens]
-Hi.
-Oh my God.
Surprise! [chuckles]
Oh.
Did I get it wrong?
Weren't you coming in next week?
No, you didn't. Honestly, babe,
you sounded like you really needed a hug.
So I told Felix I needed to leave
a week early, and it's all good.
[chuckles]
You have no idea how much I missed you.
[giggles]
Okay. [sighs]
Good luck.
Oh, come on. You got this.
And I'm gonna be right here
waiting when you're done.
I promise.
Okay.
[Katherine] You're gonna crush it.
[chuckles]
Good to see you.
There's, like, a ton of riders here.
You think you'd get a pass
'cause I trained you?
Don't get cocky.
This won't be easy. It's a big deal.
If you get this gig,
it'll be a lot of work.
Even more than you're used to right now.
And it's gonna be nights, weekends away.
Are you sure you want that?
Because if you don't…
Yeah, I want it.
You think Jackie will be happy with that?
-What do you mean?
-[Blake] Come on, Alex.
I know you two are together.
What I don't get
is why it's such a secret.
I mean, what are you afraid of?
I'm not afraid. It's just complicated.
Look, if you wanna keep going with this,
you should know that it's not easy
to have a relationship
with someone who's not in our world.
Not even if that relationship
is rock solid.
-So if it isn't--
-But it is.
So there's nothing to worry about.
Okay, then.
Let's go, cowboy.
[Alex] Mm-hmm.
[Blake chuckles]
You ready?
Well, I, uh, guess we'll find out, right?
All right, Isaac.
You good? All right, let's do it.
Hey, Cole.
Listen. I'm not playing today.
What are you talking about?
I have to take responsibility
for what I did.
I can't keep having my dad
clean up my messes.
I get this isn't great timing.
Uh, you think?
I'm sorry.
Really, man,
I hate that I'm letting the team down,
but I should've never agreed to this.
I'm just trying to do
the right thing, okay?
Isn't it a little bit late for that?
Yes. But this should be Isaac's game.
Dylan, it's the division finals.
The team needs you.
No.
They need you.
Thanks. [chuckles]
-[Katherine] Yes!
-I passed!
[both laughing]
Yes! I knew you would.
[gasps]
Oh my God. Is that…
Your mom's car. Yep.
Richard had it shipped out from New York.
-Thank you.
-[Katherine] You're welcome.
Wait. What would you
have done if I failed again?
No, we knew you weren't gonna fail.
But if you did, we would've just taken it
back to Tony's garage like the last time.
[chuckles]
[Katherine] Okay.
Go on, then.
[both chuckle]
Thank you.
[Katherine] You're welcome. Have fun.
Be safe.
[engine starts]
[sighs]
[cheering]
Whoa!
No, he won't play.
It's gonna have to be Isaac.
Okay, gentlemen, listen up.
Isaac, you need
to warm up your throwing arm.
-What?
-You're gonna be our quarterback today.
Yeah, our, uh… our number 19,
Mr. Newsome, will not be playing today.
-[players clamoring]
-Coach! Coach!
Okay, settle down. Settle down.
It'll be fine. It'll be fine.
He decided to take
his suspension seriously.
[chuckles] Hey. Come on, guys.
Just do your best.
Just do your best. Come on.
Okay? Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
-We got a football game to win.
-[player] We got this.
[cheering]
[Gordon] Dylan!
What the hell are you doing?
I was suspended, Dad.
-I shouldn't play.
-What?
After everything I did
to get you back on that team?
-Do you have any idea how hard that was?
-I know.
And I'm sorry.
Failing a drug test, you paying
to keep me on the team, it's not right.
I messed up.
I should have to face
the consequences, right? I mean,
otherwise, what does anything matter?
What matters is you playing football.
-Maybe even going pro one day.
-That's your dream, Dad.
It's not mine.
Okay, and I'm sorry
that it didn't work out for you.
But this isn't what I want.
At least not like this.
You know what?
You're probably not D1 material anyway.
[upbeat country music playing]
[bronco snorting]
♪ Some like to put on business suits… ♪
-You're up, Alex.
-[Alex] Don't worry.
I got this.
♪ Them jeans and boots ♪
♪ Turn it up country ♪
♪ Swing a little in the backwoods
Outside of town ♪
♪ Turn it up country… ♪
[man] Yah!
[horse neighing]
♪ Light up the bonfire
Light up the stake ♪
♪ Don't come with your whiskey straight ♪
♪ My friend, trouble
You just might find ♪
♪ A Tennessee honey ♪
♪ When you turn it up country ♪
♪ Yeah, we'll turn it up country ♪
[Isaac] Hut!
[coach] Come on, Garcia,
pass him the ball!
-[whistle blows]
-He wasn't ready, your cousin.
[phone ringing]
Hold on, I gotta take this.
Honey, you okay?
I'm in the middle of the game.
What? How far apart are they?
Right, okay. Yeah, I'll be right there.
Call your ma!
Okay, uh,
my wife is in labor.
-I have to go.
-Wait, but what about the game?
No, you… you… you gotta take over.
-No, I can't do that.
-Of course you can.
Just run the plays
like we practiced, all right?
And keep their spirits up.
I'm counting on you.
We all are.
[horn beeps]
[Grace chuckles]
Congratulations, driver.
Nice ride.
Thanks. It was my mom's car.
[Grace] It's so you. Can you take this?
Yeah, of course.
So, what did Alex say?
Uh, we kinda agreed
we wouldn't text or talk too much.
It might look suspicious.
Right. I mean, it's been weeks.
When are you gonna tell people
that you're together?
I don't know. Soon, I guess.
But I thought you two said
"I love you" to each other already,
so I don't really get
why you'd have to keep things a secret.
Is it because of Cole?
No.
But Cole has been acting
a little off lately.
We were supposed to do
college applications together,
but he's been spending all of his time
at Tony's or at football,
and I'm just worried
he's going to miss the deadlines.
And I thought he had retaken the SATs,
but he says
he hasn't gotten his results back,
so I don't even know if he did take them.
Maybe he did, and he just doesn't want
to tell you he did badly again.
I don't think he'd lie to me.
[Grace sighs]
Jackie, why are you
so invested in Cole's future anyways?
He's a big boy. He can handle it himself,
and you're with Alex.
Cole needs me.
Does he? Or do you need him to need you?
What do you mean?
I mean, maybe you should just pick a boy.
[Grace sighs]
Sorry. [scoffs]
You know what?
I would love it if my biggest problem
was which hot boy likes me best,
but not that there's anything going on
in my love life, of course.
Grace, is everything okay?
No.
My dad moved out.
My parents might be getting a divorce.
I didn't know.
Yeah, of course you didn't.
I'm really sorry.
It's fine.
It's okay, really.
-I gotta finish setting up the raffle.
-Are you sure I can't help?
No, thanks. I got it.
-[cheering]
-[Isaac] Hut!
[whistle blows]
Silver Falls just can't catch a break.
[announcer] Wolves touchdown by number 37.
-[whistle blows]
-[crowd clamoring]
[announcer] Wolves ball, first down.
Big tackle. Number 97,
Hughes on the 50-yard line.
[whistle blows]
[announcer] And we are going into halftime
with Aurelita in the lead.
Silver Falls are gonna have to work hard
to pull this back.
And now a very special halftime show.
Fans, let me hear you make some noise
for the team cheerleaders
from the Silver Falls Bighorns…
You okay?
What do you think?
They'd be better off without me.
It's like you said, I was just…
I was just Allen's little bitch.
I don't know what I'm doing. [chuckles]
So, what? You gonna quit?
You did.
[Dylan scoffs]
Yeah, but you're the coach.
-I can't do this.
-[Dylan] Wow.
You're really giving up that easy, huh?
You think any of this has been easy?
You think I wanted to coach
the team I used to lead?
Being on the sidelines?
Watching you throw away
all these chances I wish I still had?
I'm not giving up easy.
I'm giving up the way I do everything.
As hard as I can.
You done?
Look, man.
I know it's been rough,
but you're a good coach.
The team knows that.
You just gotta know it too.
[scoffs] Look, the guys have been giving
you shit because you're letting them.
Me walking away…
they'll get over it.
But you?
Nah, man. They look up to you.
They really do need you.
And one of us should take responsibility
for what happens to this team today.
[exhales]
Go get 'em, Coach.
[overlapping chatter]
[dance music playing]
Hey, guys!
Hey, everybody! Come on.
Everyone. Guys, quiet.
Hey! Come on.
Quiet!
[announcer] Make some noise
for the team cheerleaders…
[Cole] Okay, listen to me.
I'm not gonna lie.
It's tough out there today.
-[player 1] Yeah.
-[player 2] Yeah.
But we're tough.
We've been through much worse than this.
But right now we're playing scared,
and they can smell it on us.
Because our only hope
walked away just before the game.
Forget about that! Okay?
Okay, no one's responsible
for how this team is playing
except every player right here, right now.
The best times of my life
have been with this team,
so I know we can do this.
I know you.
Jay, Dante, when you two work together,
you're unstoppable.
We rely on you.
And TJ, if you run like I know you can,
nobody's gonna catch you.
And the rest of you? You're a team.
You're my team.
We're Bighorns.
So let's show 'em what that means!
-Are you guys with me?
-[players] Yes, Coach.
-I said, are you with me?
-Yes, Coach!
Okay!
Jay, do the honors. Break us down.
[Jay] Bighorns on three!
-One, two, three, Bighorns!
-[players] Bighorns!
[Jay] Let's go, boys!
[indistinct chatter]
Hey.
It's just like playing at home
with Parker in the yard.
-Right?
-Right.
-Right!
[whistle blows]
Hey. Everything okay over here?
Sure. Here you go.
-Grace.
-I think I really upset her.
Did you know about her parents?
She just told me.
-I wish she'd said something sooner.
-[Skylar] But that's Grace.
She never says
if something is wrong or asks for help.
She always puts
a brave face on everything.
I feel terrible.
With everything that's been going on
with Nathan and Zach,
I've been wrapped up in myself too.
Well, we have to make it up to her.
Here you go. Yeah.
Absolutely.
Okay, cowboy. That was a great ride.
-Yeah. Yeah, it felt pretty good.
-[Blake chuckles]
What did your dad think?
You're in.
-Really?
-[Blake laughs]
You know what this means?
We're teammates now.
Do you want to come celebrate
with the rest of the guys?
Uh… no, thanks.
I gotta head to the Sparkle to see Jackie.
Okay, then. Have fun.
I'll see you soon.
See you soon.
[energetic rock music playing]
Two, three, Buffalo Run!
♪ Oh, light 'em up… ♪
-[cheering]
-[whistle blows]
Extra point is good. Silver Falls
making an incredible comeback.
[cheering]
-There we go!
-[announcer] They're now in the lead.
All right! Isaac,
you can do this. Let's go!
[announcer] And Garcia coming back
onto the field, feeling the pressure here…
Red 16, Ginger. On two. Ready?
Break!
[whistle blows]
Red 16. Red 16.
Now! Hut!
♪ I wanna go with it ♪
♪ I wanna shake you up
And take over control of it… ♪
[announcer] There's the throw!
He catches it!
Keep going!
[overlapping yelling]
[Cole] Go, Isaac!
[announcer] Past the 20, down the ten!
-It's gonna be a Silver Falls touchdown!
-[cheering]
[announcer] What a trick play
from Assistant Coach Cole Walter.
And they've done it.
-Whoo!
-[player] All right, Cole!
-Let's go!
-[player] Yeah, Cole, you're the man!
[player 2] Yeah, Cole! Good job, Coach!
[players chanting] Isaac!
Isaac! Isaac! Isaac! Isaac!
[laughs] Oh my God.
Um, okay, I'll call you back.
[anticipatory music playing]
Jackie, did you hear? They won.
Isaac scored a touchdown.
Danny just called me.
-What? That's amazing!
-[Nathan] Yeah.
Jacks, one nonalcoholic mulled wine.
Thanks.
Uh, I gotta go do something.
Hi.
Hey, Nathan. Um, how are you doing?
I'm okay, I guess.
Good.
Zach wants you back, you know?
That's what it was all about.
He was never really into me at all.
I did try to warn you about him.
Zach is very good
at getting people to do what he wants.
I really don't know what happened.
I'm so sorry, Sky.
I know you are.
-I don't think you meant to hurt me.
-I really didn't.
But I do think you didn't care enough
about not hurting me
just because someone else
gave you some attention.
[exhales]
Skylar, before I met you,
no one had ever looked at me like that.
But even then, I felt like
I had to convince you to like me.
To be with me.
And I always felt like
I liked you more than you liked me.
But with Zach,
he just made me feel so wanted.
You being insecure
isn't an excuse for what you did.
I know.
But, Sky, I didn't mean it, okay?
-If we could just try again…
-What? You and me? I don't…
[Nathan] Sky.
I love you.
You know what?
I think I love you too.
But I don't think I can trust you anymore.
And I can't put myself through that again.
But it would never happen a…
Sky.
I'm sorry.
[cheering and applause]
[indistinct chatter]
[Jackie] Grace?
I'm so sorry.
I had no idea
you were going through all of that.
-It's okay.
-[Jackie] No, it's not.
I've been way too wrapped up in myself.
-No, I didn't mean that.
-[Jackie] It's okay.
I needed to hear it.
And I want to say thank you
for everything.
For the dance playlist.
For driving to see the bands.
For supporting the pop-up.
For pushing me to run for class president.
Yeah.
I couldn't have done
any of those things without you.
And I… I really want to say thank you
for taking me for ice cream
that very first day of school.
[laughs]
Yeah, well,
I can always go for ice cream, so…
[chuckles]
You never say
when something's bothering you.
-Yeah, 'cause no one cares.
-[Jackie] That is absolutely not true.
I care.
Skylar cares.
Grace, you are such a good friend,
and I've been taking you for granted.
And I'm…
I'm really sorry about your parents.
What can I do to help?
You already did. [chuckles]
Well, I'm gonna be better, okay?
And I'm gonna make it up to you.
Maybe next week we could go shopping,
and you could stay at the Walters',
and we'll order pizza.
[chuckles]
Yeah, that sounds cool. Thanks.
And for starters, I'm taking you on that.
[chuckles]
That's for children, Jackie.
So? Come on.
[Grace] Oh God.
Can we… can we hop on?
[Grace laughs]
-Okay, ready?
-You have to jump.
[Grace] Okay. Ah!
[both laugh]
[gentle, buoyant music playing]
Jackie, come here.
-What?
-I did it.
I got the sponsorship.
-You did? That's amazing!
-[Alex] Yeah.
Wait, Alex. What are you doing?
Somebody might see.
[scoffs] I don't understand
why we have to keep it a secret.
-Why can't anyone know?
-It… it's just not the right time.
But we can talk about it later, okay?
But I am.
I'm… I'm really proud of you for today.
Really.
[sighs]
[upbeat country music playing]
[Cole] Hey.
Hey.
Congratulations.
[Cole] Why aren't you over there?
That's over.
-I totally messed it up.
-How?
And how did I not know that?
Well, because I'm me,
and I said the wrong thing, obviously.
And because you're barely home nowadays.
Okay, first off,
Erin really likes you.
Okay?
And second, you gotta stop thinking
you can't just be honest with her.
Really?
Cole Walter is lecturing me
about honesty with girls.
Yep, you're right. No more advice from me.
Except this.
Don't let her go
just because you didn't try.
[gentle ballad playing]
♪ I am not okay ♪
♪ I'm barely getting by ♪
♪ I'm losing track of days ♪
♪ And losing sleep at night ♪
♪ I am not okay ♪
♪ I'm hanging on the rails ♪
♪ So if I say… ♪
I've got some snowflake ornaments there
that I made.
Yeah.
♪ I know I can't ♪
♪ Be the only one ♪
♪ Who's holding on for dear life ♪
Yeah. Thanks.
♪ And God knows I know… ♪
Congratulations on the win.
I didn't play.
-Why not?
-Because I wanna be my own person.
Does that mean
you aren't going to the showcase?
What will your dad say?
Yeah, I don't know. [chuckles]
I guess I'll find out.
But that's not important right now.
What's important is that you were right.
About what?
[cheering and applause]
Hi, everybody. Welcome. Thank you all
for coming to the Silver Falls Sparkle.
[cheering]
And now it's time for the annual
Silver Falls Sparkler Awards.
Look, I do need to take responsibility.
And, uh, yeah, I'm gonna…
I'm gonna figure it out, okay?
I know you will.
And that's why you should listen to me
'cause I'm always right.
This year, for the first time,
we are giving a Young Sparkler Award,
nominated by the junior class
of Silver Falls High.
[cheering]
[Mato] For services to the school,
including saving the canceled Fall Formal
and arranging for colleges
from all over the country
to meet with Silver Falls students.
Jackie Howard!
Jackie, come on up here.
[cheering]
-[man] Go, Jackie!
-[man 2] You deserve it, Jackie!
-[woman] Whoo!
-Whoo!
[man 3] You go, girl!
Wait.
-[chuckles] Did you know about this?
-You go, girl!
Now, please join me
in showing our appreciation
to all of our Silver Falls Sparklers!
[cheering and applause]
You know,
I don't know anyone like you, Kiley.
Well, you've been hanging out
with cheerleaders for far too long.
Wait, let me speak.
I'm trying to… say something.
Okay. [chuckles]
And finally,
the moment we've all been waiting for.
I think you're pretty cool, Kiley.
[electricity crackles]
[cheering and applause]
And I think I'm a little bit crazy
about you.
Well, you're definitely crazy.
[crowd] Oh!
[cheering and applause]
Oh my God.
-Great.
-[Kiley chuckles]
They came.
-And tried to get us to just eat--
-Erin?
Look, uh,
I get that you don't see a future with me,
and that's fine.
-Really.
-No, it's not…
That's not it.
We're so young,
and I think we might be headed
in different directions.
And I do believe in you.
You should go after your dreams,
but so should I.
Yeah.
I don't want to be the girl
that held you back.
[Danny] I would never
think of you like that.
And you're right,
our dreams… are different,
but that's okay.
So why don't we just try to enjoy
what we have for now?
You know, we can worry
about the future when it's here.
I'd like that.
Yeah.
All right.
[upbeat music playing]
♪ Hope floats ♪
♪ Up and down the Pacific coast ♪
♪ Ooh, faith ♪
♪ Needs ♪
♪ Best, it's best to set ourselves free ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ When we stick together ♪
♪ The light is found ♪
♪ Tell me now or never
We're safe and sound… ♪
Breathing.
Hey!
♪ When we stick together… ♪
One, two, three.
Thanks, Terry.
Cheers.
Oh, hi! Can I see it?
Yeah.
[Katherine] Oh!
I hope you know how much you deserve this.
Yeah, well.
Listen, I know that the last few months
haven't exactly been easy for you, but
you're such a huge part
of this community and our family.
Thanks for coming back to us.
Thank you for persuading me
to come back to you.
I'm just glad
that everything's working out.
I mean, it almost feels like
everything's getting back to normal.
♪ We're safe and sound ♪
♪ When we stick together… ♪
[song fades]
There she is.
One sec.
Jackie, congrats on the award.
Thanks.
Was it you?
No.
And I'm sworn to secrecy.
I think you should go for
student council president next year.
What? No. I tried running
for junior class president.
-And look how well that turned out.
-Everyone knows who should've won.
And anyways,
I think you'll have a pretty easy run
at student council president
because I'm gonna make you VP
as of next semester.
-You can do that?
-Sure.
Thanks.
You deserve it.
[Danny] It's good. I'm proud of you.
[Cole] Let's see what happens next.
[Jackie] Hey.
Hey.
I'm just gonna, uh…
Hey, Erin, wait up.
Uh, congratulations.
Yeah. Thanks.
Um…
-You too.
-Thanks.
Are you happy?
[Cole] I am.
It, uh… it felt good this time.
Great. That's great.
I, um…
I'll see you at home. Okay?
Okay.
[emotional music playing]
[Will sighs]
I just don't think I can get past this.
I invested everything into this project.
I really wanted it to work.
I think it would've worked.
But now it's just gone.
And my dad took it away.
Yeah.
What am I supposed to do now?
You know, the… the farm I was at
was in the middle of nowhere.
And we slept in tents,
and some days there was no electricity,
and other days the food would run low,
and we would just hope
that supply trucks were on their way.
-Yeah. Yeah, I know. It sounded awful.
-[Hayley] No.
No, it was great.
Not when the toilet was backed up
for three days. That was awful.
But most of the time. [chuckles]
There is a whole world out there,
and we haven't seen any of it.
What if this town is
just too small for your big ideas?
[pop music playing inside]
-Danny, go.
-[Nathan] I'll teach you about a C chord.
-The C chord?
-[Nathan] It's the most basic chord.
-It's your turn.
-I know how to do an ollie.
-Uh, hey, Jackie, you want to sit here?
-Yeah, thanks.
[Isaac] Why not try and do an ollie?
Hey, can I interview you
for my People of Influence assignment?
-Sure, Jordan.
-[Jordan] Thanks.
[Lee] How much can you really learn…
So… now that you passed your driving test…
I'll soon be your own personal chauffeur,
just like I promised.
-Okay.
-[Danny] Do you have any twos?
Hey, guys, is Mom around?
-[Lee] She had to go out on a call.
-And where's Dad?
-[Nathan] He's up on the top field.
-At this time of night?
Yeah, he's been up there all afternoon.
Thanks. Hey, and congrats.
Appreciate you guys. All of you.
Hey, while we're congratulating everyone,
Cole got his new SAT scores.
Cole? What did you get?
Just like a 1250.
That's amazing. When did you get them?
Couple weeks ago.
But I… I thought…
Why didn't you say anything?
You know what? Um, you guys celebrate.
I'm going out.
Cole?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Can we not do this again?
I know you're not fine.
You've been off with me for weeks.
You've been avoiding me,
staying out of the house,
and we were supposed to do
college applications together,
but you don't tell me
you got your SAT scores?
Just, please, be honest with me.
[Cole chuckles]
Oh, like you've been honest with me?
What are you talking about?
I have been honest with you.
I don't think
you've even been honest with yourself.
Okay, Cole.
Okay.
Here's some honesty for you.
I saw you and Alex
at Richard's.
[somber music playing]
You know,
I was giving you space, like you asked.
But I thought we had something.
I've been racking my brain
trying to understand why
you'd be with my brother again.
We said that we were going to be friends.
We've never just been friends.
Cole, this is not…
-Me and Alex, we're--
-What?
Why is it you can't stay away from him,
but you can stay away from me?
I can't… stay away from you, okay?
I keep trying to, and nothing works.
And I… I can't have that, Cole.
I can't be with someone who makes me feel
the way that you make me feel.
-How do I make you feel?
-Stop it.
I love you, Jackie.
And I thought you felt the same way,
but if I'm wrong, then just… just say it.
I love you.
Okay?
Are we done? Can I go now?
Why would being with me be so awful?
What is it?
When we kissed before,
it was the only time that I've ever
stopped thinking about everything.
How I'm doing in school, if I fit in here,
what my future will look like.
I felt really… free,
like I was out of control,
and… and I can't have that, Cole.
I can't. I can't lose control.
Why?
Because…
♪ My mother said I'm too romantic… ♪
I don't know what might happen if I do.
♪ I only started to believe her… ♪
[Alex] You love him?
♪ I don't say… ♪
Alex…
♪ But still you take my breath ♪
♪ And still the things I know… ♪
Hey, what's going on?
It's Dad.
♪ From out of the cold ♪
♪ Fire on fire ♪
♪ Would normally kill us ♪
♪ But this much desire ♪
♪ Together we're winners ♪
♪ They say that we're out of control ♪
♪ And some say we're sinners ♪
♪ But don't let them ruin ♪
♪ Our beautiful rhythms ♪
♪ 'Cause when you unfold me ♪
♪ And tell me you love me ♪
♪ Then look in my eyes ♪
♪ You are perfection ♪
♪ My only direction ♪
♪ It's fire on fire ♪
♪ You are perfection, my only direction ♪
Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org